vigoindustries.com 2014-11-23

# VIGO - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

**DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO OTHERS**  
Except in the limited circumstances stated in this paragraph, we do not sell, rent, license, trade or otherwise disclose the personal information of our Web site visitors to unaffiliated third parties. We may disclose your information to service providers who assist us in operating the Web site or conducting our business. We may also share such information among our subsidiaries and affiliates as necessary to provide you with the information and services you request or in which you may otherwise be interested. We may disclose information about you if and when we believe it is necessary to comply with any law, rule, court order, or subpoena, or to enforce our legal rights or the rules of this Web site, or to protect our business, property and operations, or in connection with a sale, acquisition, merger or other business combination of our business with a third party. We may also disclose nonpersonally identifiable visitor information to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

Some areas of the Web site may allow you to conduct e-commerce transactions (event registration, donation, etc.). In connection with these transactions, we collect data necessary to complete the transaction that is furnished by you. This information may be furnished to a third party in order to facilitate the transaction.

 **LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
We may create links to other Web sites that we think may be of interest to you. We do not endorse any other Web sites, and our privacy policy applies only to your use of our Web site. We have not reviewed the privacy policies of any Web sites we link to our Web site, and you should read the privacy policies of each site you visit to determine what information that site may collect about you.

 **SECURITY**  
Since we are committed to your privacy and security, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to attempt to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. However, please remember that no transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us or from us, and you do so at your own risk. When you place an order or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once we receive your transmission, we use our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

 **CHANGES IN VIGO'S PRIVACY POLICY**  
By using our Web site, you consent to our collection and the use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy and procedures, we will post these changes on our Web site. You have the opportunity to review privacy policy each time you use the Web site so that you are aware of any modifications made to these policies.
